Happy New Year, Jay.
새해 복 많이 받으세요, 제이.
I feel like I’m going crazy.
미칠 것 같은 느낌이 들어요.
Or am I already crazy?
아니면 내가 이미 미친 걸까?
So much has happened ever since I wore this uniform.
그 이후로 너무 많은 일이 일어났어요 나는 이 유니폼을 입었다.
Section E!!!
섹션 E!!!
Why did you even do that, Jay-jay?
왜 그랬어요, 제이제이?
You almost got carried away!
당신은 거의 흥분했습니다!
You really are crazy!
당신은 정말 미쳤어요!
You’re weak!
당신은 약해요!
Later I’m going to see the King of Assholes,
나중에 나는 멍청이들의 왕을 보세요,
and after that…
그 후에는…
I already accepted Yuri’s proposal,
나는 이미 유리의 제안을 받아들였다.
so I shouldn’t have done that to Keifer.
그러니 케이퍼에게 그런 짓을 하면 안 됐어요.
Control yourself, Jay.
스스로를 통제하세요, 제이.
Jay?
어치?
Yes?
예?
Wow!
우와!
Jay, the room looks so nice.
제이, 방 정말 좋아 보여요.
Is this part of your New Year's resolution?
이것이 새해 결심의 일부인가요?
Yes, Auntie. A new look for a new life.
응, 이모. 새로운 삶을 위한 새로운 모습.
By the way, Yuri asked for permission.
그건 그렇고, 유리는 허락을 구했다.
He said he'll pick you up, he's probably downstairs already.
그 사람이 당신을 데리러 갈 거라고 하더군요. 그 사람은 아마 이미 아래층에 있을 거예요.
Ah okay, I'll go down in a while.
아 알겠습니다. 잠시 후 내려갈게요.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Yuri…
유리…
Right.
오른쪽.
I’m already engaged, so I shouldn’t be thinking about Keifer anymore.
난 이미 약혼했으니 그러면 안 되지 더 이상 Keifer에 대해 생각하지 마세요.
You can do this, Jay-jay.
넌 할 수 있어, 제이제이.
Let’s just forget what happened on New Year’s.
그냥 잊어버리자 새해에 무슨 일이 있었는지.
Good morning.
좋은 아침이에요.
Give that to me, I’ll carry it.
그거 나한테 줘, 내가 가져갈게.
No, it’s fine. It's not heavy.
아니요, 괜찮아요. 무겁지 않아요.
Why did you pick me up? I can bike on my own.
왜 나를 데리러 왔어요? 나는 혼자서 자전거를 탈 수 있다.
Of course—fiancé duties.
물론이죠. 약혼자의 의무죠.
Fiancé…
약혼자…
Shit, it sounds so heavy.
젠장, 너무 무거워 보이는데.
I’m not used to it.
나는 그것에 익숙하지 않습니다.
Let’s go.
갑시다.
No.
아니요.
She’s not going with you.
그녀는 당신과 함께 가지 않을 것입니다.
Leave.
떠나다.
You're not the one who's going to decide here.
당신은 그 사람이 아니다 여기서 누가 결정할까요?
Aries, it’s okay. I also want to talk to Yuri.
양자리, 괜찮아. 나도 유리랑 얘기하고 싶어.
If you had just listened to me,
방금 내 말을 들었다면
you wouldn’t have been set up in that engagement.
넌 그러지 않았을 거야 그 약혼에서 설정되었습니다.
Right?
오른쪽?
Engagement...
약혼...
Set-up...
설정...
Let's go.
갑시다.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
You’ve been quiet.
당신은 조용했습니다.
Of course, I’m fine.
물론이죠. 저는 괜찮습니다.
Have you talked to Angelo yet?
안젤로랑 얘기해봤어?
I'm not ready to talk to him yet.
난 아직 그 사람과 얘기할 준비가 안 됐어요.
I'm sorry, Jay.
미안해요, 제이.
I wasn’t honest about my feelings for you.
나는 솔직하지 못했다 당신에 대한 내 감정.
But from now on, I’ll be more honest.
하지만 지금부터, 좀 더 솔직하게 말할게요.
We’re engaged.
우리는 약혼했어요.
So I should also be honest with him about what happened on New Year’s.
그러니 나도 그 사람에게 솔직하게 말해야 해 새해에 일어난 일에 대해.
Uhmm, I need to confess something—
음, 고백할 게 있는데—
Is it about Keifer?
키퍼에 관한 것인가요?
It's okay, Jay.
괜찮아, 제이.
I don’t want to hear it anymore.
더 이상 듣고 싶지 않아요.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
You don’t need to apologize.
사과할 필요는 없습니다.
I understand you,
이해해요,
but I’ll wait for you Jay no matter how long.
하지만 기다릴게 Jay 아무리 오랫동안.
Even until the day of our wedding.
결혼식 당일까지도요.
If that's what it takes.
그것이 필요한 경우입니다.
Yuri.
유리.
I'm okay, Jay.
난 괜찮아, 제이.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
My only wish is that you give me a chance.
내 유일한 소원은 그것뿐이야 당신은 나에게 기회를 줘.
Please don't close off your heart.
마음을 닫지 마시기 바랍니다.
I hope you still choose me in the end.
그래도 결국에는 나를 선택해주셨으면 좋겠습니다.
Honestly,
솔직히,
I don’t even know what I feel for Yuri.
나는 유리에 대해 어떤 감정을 갖고 있는지조차 모른다.
Is it guilt?
죄책감인가요?
Because he’s kind to me?
그 사람이 나한테 친절해서?
Or is it because of my obligation to my family?
아니면 그것 때문인가? 가족에 대한 나의 의무는?
Ugh, whatever. Whatever happens, happens.
어, 뭐든지. 무슨 일이 일어나든 일어난다.
Uhm...
음...
How are we going to tell our classmates?
우리는 어떻게 갈 것인가? 우리 반 친구들에게 말할까?
I don’t think they need to know.
나는 그들이 알 필요가 없다고 생각합니다.
Why?
왜?
It’ll just cause chaos if they find out—
그들이 알면 혼란만 야기할 뿐—
especially since they know Keifer has feelings for you.
특히 그들은 알고 있기 때문에 키퍼는 당신에 대한 감정을 가지고 있습니다.
Yeah, you’re right. It might cause trouble.
응, 네 말이 맞아. 문제가 발생할 수 있습니다.
Great idea.
좋은 생각이에요.
There.
거기.
That’s good.
좋아요.
Ouch!
아야!
What was that for?
그건 무엇을 위한 것이었나요?
I don’t want things to be awkward between us, Jay.
나는 물건을 원하지 않는다 우리 사이가 어색해지다니, 제이.
Act like the same Jay you are whenever we’re together,
당신과 같은 Jay처럼 행동하세요 우리가 함께 있을 때마다
and I'll do the same.
나도 똑같이 할 거예요.
You’re right.
당신 말이 맞아요.
Ouch! That really hurts!
아야! 정말 아파요!
That’s not enough— want one on your forehead too?
그것만으로는 충분하지 않습니다. 네 이마에도 하나 바르고 싶어?
Come on, let’s go. We might be late.
자, 가자. 우리가 늦을 수도 있어요.
Wait, wait, wait.
잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐.
- What? - I forgot something.
- 무엇? - 잊어버린 게 있어요.
What?
무엇?
I'll go ahead.
나는 계속할 것이다.
Can I ask for one more favor?
부탁 하나만 더 해도 될까요?
What?
무엇?
Can you stop picking me up and taking me home?
나 좀 그만 데리러 갈래? 그리고 나를 집에 데려다주겠다고?
Someone might, you know, notice.
누군가는, 알다시피, 알아두세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Okay, Jay-jay. We'll do what is right.
알았어, 제이제이. 우리는 옳은 일을 할 것입니다.
You're already engaged to Yuri, time to forget about Keif—
유리랑 이미 약혼했잖아 Keif를 잊을 시간—
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
Tss. Profanity on the first day back?
쯧쯧. 욕설 사용 돌아온 첫날?
Or did you just miss my lips?
아니면 내 입술이 그리웠나요?
What? Keifer!
무엇? 키퍼!
- Stop this. - Why?
- 그만해요. - 왜?
- What do you mean "why"? Keifer, please. - Stop what?
- "왜"라는 게 무슨 뜻이에요? 키퍼, 제발요. - 뭘 그만둬?
This! What you're doing right now. Stop flirting with me.
이것! 당신이 지금 무엇을하고 있는지. 나한테 장난 좀 그만쳐
What's wrong if I flirt with you?
내가 너한테 장난치면 어떡하지?
What's wrong if I flirt with the one I love?
내가 바람피우면 어떡하지? 내가 좋아하는 사람이랑?
It's wrong.
틀렸어.
It's as if I'm cheating on Yuri.
마치 유리를 속이는 것 같아요.
We're already engaged,
우리는 이미 약혼했어요
stay away from me.
나에게서 떨어져있어.
Cheating?
부정 행위?
We're not in a relationship.
우리는 관계에 있지 않습니다.
So how are we cheating on him?
그렇다면 우리는 어떻게 그를 속이고 있습니까?
You're not cheating on Yuri
넌 유리를 속이는 게 아니야
because we're not in a relationship.
왜냐하면 우리는 관계에 있지 않기 때문입니다.
If that's the case, then leave me alone!
그렇다면, 그럼 날 내버려둬!
We're not in a relationship, but…
우리는 사귀는 사이는 아니지만…
you are mine.
당신은 내 것입니다.
You know what, you're crazy.
그거 알아요, 당신은 미쳤어요.
Crazy for you?
당신을 위해 미친?
Yeah, I think so.
네, 그런 것 같아요.
I’ll wait for you Jay no matter how long.
언제까지라도 Jay를 기다릴게요.
Even until the day of our wedding.
결혼식 당일까지도요.
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
You'll pay for this!
당신은 이것에 대한 비용을 지불합니다!
Welcome back, bro!
돌아온 걸 환영해요, 형제님!
Come on, hurry, let’s play.
자, 빨리, 놀자.
Jay!
어치!
How was vacation?
휴가는 어땠나요?
It was okay. How about you and Mica?
괜찮았어요. 당신과 미카는 어때요?
Obviously they ran out of condoms again—
분명히 또 콘돔이 떨어졌어요—
he even asked me for some. Said it wasn’t enough.
그는 심지어 나에게 몇 가지를 요청했습니다. 충분하지 않다고 하더군요.
- He asked you? - Idiot!
- 그가 당신한테 물어봤나요? - 바보!
Asshole!
항문!
Unbelievable!
믿을 수 없는!
- Ouch! - Hey, Jay!
- 아야! - 안녕, 제이!
Everyone already went on vacation but you're still sour.
다들 벌써 휴가 갔네 하지만 당신은 여전히 ​​시큼합니다.
Didn't you—
그렇지 않았나요—
Stop it! It’s New Year, have you changed?
그만해요! 새해인데, 달라졌나요?
- Of course, man! - Yeah right!
- 물론이지! - 응 맞아!
He gambled all his Christmas money.
그는 크리스마스 돈을 모두 도박에 썼습니다.
- Obviously. - You're really something, huh.
- 확실히. - 넌 정말 대단해, ​​응.
You don't have money!
당신은 돈이 없습니다!
Hey, hey! What’s going on?
이봐, 이봐! 무슨 일이야?
How’s Grace?
그레이스는 잘 지내요?
She has lots of cravings.
그녀는 갈망이 많습니다.
- She's always hungry. - That’s normal.
- 그녀는 항상 배가 고프다. - 그건 정상이에요.
Just like you.
당신처럼.
Oh really?
오, 진짜?
Ouch.
아야.
- Too early in the morning. - You’re already annoying this early!
- 너무 이른 아침이에요. - 이렇게 일찍부터 짜증나잖아!
Jay!
어치!
Collect everyone’s contribution for the food.
모두의 기여도를 수집하세요 음식을 위해.
Ignored? What’s his problem?
무시했나요? 그의 문제는 무엇입니까?
Hey, where’s Ci-N?
저기, Ci-N은 어디 있어?
He’s not here. He’s not answering my calls.
그는 여기 없어요. 그는 내 전화에 응답하지 않습니다.
Huh? What happened to him?
뭐? 그에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Should I go to their house later?
나중에 그 사람 집에 가야 하나?
But what if his grumpy brother is there?
하지만 그 사람이 심술궂으면 어쩌지? 형 거기 있어?
Hi, Jay!
안녕, 제이!
Damn!
젠장!
What happened to your lip, bro?
입술은 어떻게 된 거야, 형?
Did you get into a fight?
싸웠나요?
Looks like your lips saw some action, Keif.
입술같아 어떤 행동을 봤어요, 케이프.
You want some lip balm?
립밤 좀 드릴까요?
You deserve it.
당신은 그럴 자격이 있습니다.
Tss.
쯧쯧.
Hey, what's up.
안녕, 무슨 일이야?
- Rory! - Hey!
- 로리! - 여기요!
If you look at us, it seems like nothing has changed.
우리를 보면, 아무것도 변하지 않은 것 같습니다.
Hey, that didn’t hit!
야, 그거 안 맞았어!
Throw it!
던져라!
Asshole! Hey asshole!
항문! 이봐, 멍청아!
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
Chill with that.
진정하세요.
But the truth is, a lot has already changed.
하지만 진실은, 이미 많은 것이 변했습니다.
- Hey, bro. - Ah!
- 안녕, 형. - 아!
Settle down, settle down.
진정하세요, 진정하세요.
Welcome back, class!
돌아온 걸 환영해요, 수업!
We’ve already started planning your retreat.
우리는 이미 시작했어요 퇴각을 계획하고 있습니다.
We’re included in that, Sir?
우리도 거기에 포함되어 있습니다, 선생님?
All students join the retreat before graduating.
모든 학생들이 수련회에 참여합니다. 졸업하기 전에.
For real? So we’re actually graduating?
진짜요? 그럼 우리 진짜 졸업하는 거야?
All I can say is,
내가 말할 수 있는 건,
there will be lots of activities during the retreat.
많은 활동이 있을 거예요 퇴각 중.
When is it, Sir?
선생님, 언제세요?
No definite date yet, but earlier than the usual retreat.
아직 확정된 날짜는 없지만, 하지만 평소의 퇴각보다 일찍.
It’s just a bit tricky because of the post-final exams.
좀 까다롭기 때문에 기말고사 이후의 시험.
What’s the post-final exams?
기말고사 이후에는 어떤 시험이 있나요?
There’s a fifth exam.
다섯번째 시험이 있어요.
And that determines whether a student passes or not.
그리고 그것이 여부를 결정합니다. 학생이 합격하든 안 하든.
Huh?
뭐?
Why is there even a fifth exam?
왜 다섯 번째 시험이 있습니까?
So if a student doesn’t pass, they won’t graduate?
그래서 만약 학생이 합격하지 못한다면, 그 사람들 졸업 안 할 거야?
Don’t worry Jay, I got you.
걱정하지 마세요 Jay, 내가 잡았어요.
You will graduate.
졸업하게 됩니다.
Food, food, food!
음식, 음식, 음식!
That's all?
그게 다야?
That’s all we have left.
그게 우리에게 남은 전부입니다.
You guys still haven’t pitched in for the groceries.
여러분 아직 못했어요 식료품을 사러 나섰습니다.
- True! - You’re really something, huh!
- 진실! - 넌 정말 대단해, ​​응!
Alright, alright.
알았어, 알았어.
Wow, you're quick to dodge when it's time to chip in!
와, 피하는 게 빠르구나 칩을 넣을 시간이 되면!
Do you hear anything?
아무것도 들리나요?
One at a time!
한 번에 하나씩!
Fine, here.
좋아요, 여기요.
- Let's split it. - Ah!
- 나눠보자. - 아!
Plate.
그릇.
Dish.
접시.
Rice.
쌀.
More.
더.
Just eat it already.
그냥 먹어요.
Move aside.
옆으로 비켜가세요.
And if I don’t want to?
내가 원하지 않는다면?
Do you want me to tell them what we did last New Year’s Eve?
내가 그들에게 무엇을 말해주기를 원하시나요? 우리 지난 설날에 그랬어요?
What do you want?
당신은 무엇을 원하세요?
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
You just look cute when you eat.
먹는 모습만 봐도 귀엽네요.
Is it bad to watch?
보는 것이 나쁜가요?
Yes! Go away!
예! 저리 가요!
Bro, let's share.
형, 공유하자.
All of that is yours?
그거 다 네 거야?
Is there a problem, Jay?
문제라도 있어, 제이?
Ah nothing, he’s just teasing me.
아 아무것도 아니야, 그 사람은 그냥 나를 놀리는 거야.
You sure?
정말요?
Remember, you are mine.
기억하세요, 당신은 내 것입니다.
Jay!
어치!
No one follow me!
아무도 따라오지 않아!
No one is following you.
아무도 당신을 따르지 않습니다.
There, nice!
거기, 좋아요!
So refreshing!
정말 상쾌해요!
I'm sure nobody will bother me here.
여기서는 아무도 나를 괴롭히지 않을 것이라고 확신합니다.
Let me call that brat.
그 놈한테 전화 좀 할게요.
He won’t answer.
그는 대답하지 않을 것입니다.
Ugh!
윽!
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
Who’s that?
누구야?
Oh, Edrix!
아, 에드릭스!
I thought it was someone else!
다른 사람인 줄 알았어요!
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
I just couldn’t help it.
나는 그것을 도울 수 없었다.
Do you have a problem?
문제가 있나요?
I’m mad at myself!
나 자신에게 화가 났어요!
I'm such a coward!
나는 정말 겁쟁이 야!
Why?
왜?
Unrequited love is just so damn hard!
짝사랑은 그저 정말 힘들어!
I can’t even tell her…
그녀에게 말할 수도 없어요…
or show her.
아니면 그녀에게 보여주세요.
Yeah, that’s really hard.
응, 그거 정말 힘들어.
But at least you’re sure.
하지만 적어도 당신은 확신합니다.
It’s only one person.
단 한 사람뿐입니다.
It's harder when you're stuck between two.
막히면 더 힘들어요 둘 사이.
But who is it anyway?
그런데 대체 누구죠?
Wow, she’s pretty!
와, 정말 예쁘네요!
Freya really is pretty.
프레야는 정말 예쁘네요.
Yeah, she’s really—WHAT?
응, 그 사람 정말- 뭐?
That's Freya?
그거 프레야야?
F-Freya is the one you’re talking about?
F-프레야가 그 사람이야 너 말하는거야?
Yeah.
응.
It's been a long time Jay.
오랜만이에요 제이.
Wow, what a revelation.
와, 정말 놀라운 계시네요.
But...
하지만...
let’s keep this between us, okay?
이건 우리끼리만 하자, 알았지?
Promise?
약속하다?
You don’t have food?
음식이 없나요?
That’s food?
그게 음식이에요?
Yeah, we were eating downstairs.
응, 우리는 아래층에서 먹고 있었어.
And you’re here being dramatic.
그리고 당신은 여기서 극적으로 행동하고 있습니다.
Whose is this?
이것은 누구의 것입니까?
- Auntie, I’m really starving promise. - Looks like it.
- 아줌마, 정말 배고파요 약속해요. - 그런 것 같아요.
Don’t worry, there’s another box there.
걱정하지 마세요. 거기에 또 다른 상자가 있습니다.
All of that is for you.
그 모든 것은 당신을 위한 것입니다.
We have a visitor?
방문객이 있나요?
Relax, there’s more in the kitchen.
진정하세요. 주방에는 더 많은 것이 있습니다.
- This tastes so good, Auntie. - Good?
- 이거 정말 맛있어요, 이모. - 좋은?
Ci-N?
Ci-N?
You idiot!
바보야!
What happened to you?
당신에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Do you know how worried I was, you brat?!
어떻게 하는지 아세요? 걱정했어, 이 자식아?!
Really?
정말?
You were concerned about me?
나 걱정했지?
Wow, you’re so sweet, Jay.
와, 너 정말 사랑스러워, 제이.
Don’t be like that, Jay-jay!
그러지 마, 제이제이!
Sorry, Auntie.
미안해요, 아줌마.
This kid didn't attend school today.
이 아이는 오늘 학교에 가지 않았습니다.
I’ll leave you two to catch up.
따라잡을 수 있도록 두 분을 남겨 두겠습니다.
I’ll prepare dinner.
내가 저녁을 준비할게.
Thank you, Auntie.
고마워요, 아줌마.
You've got some nerve!
당신은 약간의 용기를 가지고 있습니다!
Enjoying the food too much, huh?
음식을 너무 즐기고 있는 걸까요?
Why weren’t you in class?
왜 수업에 없었나요?
It hurts, Jay!
아파, 제이!
- Oh really! - I’ll tell Auntie!
- 오, 진짜! - 이모한테 말할게!
What happened to you?
당신에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
What’s the problem?
문제가 무엇입니까?
Because…
왜냐면...
my brother locked me up.
내 동생이 나를 가두었어요.
He said...
그가 말하길...
he’s sending me to London because I keep on causing trouble.
그 사람이 나를 런던으로 보낸다 내가 계속 문제를 일으키기 때문이다.
Said I’m wasting my potential.
내 잠재력을 낭비하고 있다고 말했어요.
Of course I wasn’t going to allow that.
물론이다 나는 그것을 허용하지 않을 것입니다.
So yeah, he locked me in my room.
그럼요, 그는 나를 내 방에 가두었습니다.
I was worried about you.
나는 당신에 대해 걱정했다.
Sorry…
미안…
He confiscated my gadgets,
그 사람이 내 장비를 압수했어요
I couldn’t message you.
메시지를 보낼 수 없었습니다.
Is that all he did?
그 사람이 한 게 그게 다야?
He didn't hit you?
그 사람이 당신을 때리지 않았나요?
No!
아니요!
You know why?
이유를 아시나요?
Why?
왜?
Because I ran away.
왜냐하면 나는 도망쳤기 때문이다.
- Seriously? - Yeah.
- 진지하게? - 응.
He said if I won’t listen, I should just leave.
내가 듣지 않으면, 그는 말했다. 난 그냥 떠나야겠어.
Where would you go?
어디로 갈 건가요?
Here. With you!
여기. 당신과 함께!
That’s not allowed, are you crazy?!
그건 안 돼, 미쳤어?!
Why not? Angelo said it was okay.
왜 안 돼? 안젤로는 괜찮다고 했어요.
What Angelo?
무슨 안젤로?
You made that up!
당신이 그걸 만들어냈어요!
Right Angelo, it’s okay?
그렇지 안젤로, 괜찮아?
Yes, that’s true.
네, 맞습니다.
Oh—see?
아— 알겠어요?
That hurts!
아파요!
My new home.
나의 새 집.
Won’t they look for you?
그들이 당신을 찾지 않을까요?
No, Mom knows.
아니, 엄마는 알아요.
I told her.
나는 그녀에게 말했다.
Wow.
우와.
Of all the people who left home, you're the only one who asked for permission.
집을 떠난 모든 사람들 중에서 당신은 허락을 구한 유일한 사람.
Amazing.
놀라운.
Of course— so Mom knows where I’m going.
물론이죠— 그래서 엄마는 내가 어디로 가는지 알고 있어요.
Where are you even going to sleep?
도대체 어디서 자러 가나요?
Angelo said in your room.
안젤로가 네 방에서 말했다.
My room?
내 방?
- Do you want some? - Yeah.
- 좀 드실래요? - 응.
Race you to your room!
당신의 방으로 달려가세요!
Idiot! No eating there!
바보! 거기에서는 식사를 할 수 없습니다!
Hey!
여기요!
Ci-N!
Ci-N!
[Ci-N singing]
[씨엔 노래]
Good morning.
좋은 아침이에요.
Get up! Your pillow is soaked with your drool.
일어나세요! 베개가 침으로 흠뻑 젖었습니다.
Ci-N, you're so noisy!
Ci-N, 너 너무 시끄러워!
So early in the morning!
그러니까 아침 일찍!
I'll go ahead, Jay.
내가 먼저 갈게, 제이.
Going downstairs to eat.
먹으러 아래층으로 내려갑니다.
Wow, feel at home.
와, 집에 온 것 같은 느낌이 드네요.
Ouch.
아야.
Did Aries do something to you?
양자리가 당신에게 무슨 짓을 했나요?
What? What did he do?
무엇? 그는 무엇을 했나요?
Let’s go.
갑시다.
Huh?
뭐?
Ci, wait—talk to me.
Ci, 잠깐만요. 나한테 얘기 좀 해보세요.
What did Aries do to you?
양자리가 당신에게 무슨 짓을 했나요?
Is it true, Jay?
사실이야, 제이?
You’re leaving Section E?
섹션 E를 떠나시나요?
Did Aries tell you that?
양자리가 그렇게 말했나요?
He said I should stay away from you because you’re leaving.
그는 내가 멀리 있어야 한다고 말했어 당신이 떠나기 때문에 당신에게서.
No, don’t stay away from me.
아니, 나에게서 멀어지지 마세요.
- Crazy. - Don’t listen to him.
- 미친. - 그 사람 말을 듣지 마세요.
Who said that?
누가 그런 말을 했나요?
Who said you'll leave Section E?
누가 섹션 E를 떠날 거라고 말했나요?
Who's fighting?
누가 싸우고 있나요?
Is there a cockfight?
닭싸움이 있나요?
Jay, you’re leaving Section E?
Jay, 섹션 E를 떠나는 거야?
No!
아니요!
But that’s what he said!
그런데 그 사람이 그렇게 말하더군요!
Why would he say that?
왜 그렇게 말하겠습니까?
You don’t want to be with us anymore, Jay?
넌 같이 있고 싶지 않아 이제 우리는 더 이상 없나요, 제이?
We can still tolerate your sour attitude.
우리는 여전히 당신의 신랄한 태도를 용인할 수 있습니다.
I thought we were solid Section E.
나는 우리가 섹션 E에 충실하다고 생각했어요.
- Ouch! - Yeah.
- 아야! - 응.
We thought nothing could break us.
우리는 아무것도 우리를 무너뜨릴 수 없다고 생각했습니다.
- Exactly. - So dramatic!
- 정확히. - 정말 드라마틱해요!
It’s not like that!
그렇지 않아요!
Was it Aries?!
양자리였나요?!
Keifer, stop!
키퍼, 그만해!
Jay, don’t leave! Stay in Section E!
제이, 떠나지 마! 섹션 E에 머무르세요!
- Don’t leave! - Ci, enough!
- 떠나지 마세요! - Ci, 그만해!
- I don’t care! - Jay, please don’t!!
- 상관없어요! - 제이, 그러지 마세요!!
What is happening here?!
여기서 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?!
Jay-jay is leaving Section E!
제이제이가 섹션 E를 떠납니다!
- Stop! - Jay, please!
- 멈추다! - 제이, 제발!
Is that true?
그게 사실인가요?
I’m not!
나는 그렇지 않다!
Look—I’ll explain later!
보세요. 나중에 설명하겠습니다!
Go to Keifer first, he might go after Aries! Hurry!
먼저 케이퍼로 가세요. 그는 양자리를 쫓을 수도 있습니다! 서두르다!
- Ci, no one's leaving! - Jay please please!
- 씨, 아무도 안 가! - 제이 제발요!
I’m not leaving!
나는 떠나지 않을 것이다!
- So dramatic! - Really?
- 정말 드라마틱해요! - 정말?
Yes! That's what I've been saying!
예! 그게 내가 말한 거야!
Aries told me to choose:
양자리가 선택하라고 했어요:
Either I leave Section E,
섹션 E를 떠나거나
or he won't give me my Dad's number.
아니면 그 사람이 나한테 안 줄 거야 우리 아빠 전화번호.
But I chose you guys, okay?! Happy now?!
하지만 난 너희들을 선택했어, 알았지?! 이제 행복해?!
Let's go, we need to follow Keifer!
가자, 키퍼를 따라가야 해!
Hurry!
서두르다!
- Let’s go! - I don’t want to! Why?
- 갑시다! -하고 싶지 않아! 왜?
Are you paying me for this? I don't want to!
나한테 돈을 주는 거야? 나는 원하지 않는다!
Get up!
일어나세요!
Come here.
이리 오세요.
Is that it, huh?!
그게 다야, 응?!
Let's go, quickly!
가자, 빨리!
What? Let's finish this here now!
무엇? 이제 여기서 끝내자!
Okay, let's end it here.
좋아, 여기서 끝내자.
Can someone stop them?!
누군가 그들을 막을 수 있을까요?!
Enough! Stop it already!
충분한! 이제 그만해요!
I guess the rumors are true, it's really a mess here.
소문이 사실인 것 같은데, 여기는 정말 엉망이에요.
Can those losers get out of here already?
그 패배자들은 벌써 여기서 나갈 수 있을까?
Especially you!
특히 당신!
Enough! Don't you dare speak to Jay-jay like that!
충분한! 감히 제이제이에게 그런 말을 하지 마세요!
Jay-jay, you need to leave.
제이제이, 넌 떠나야 해.
Things are getting out of control because of you.
일이 빠져나가고 있어 너 때문에 통제해.
As if.
마치.
Stop it already, let's go.
이제 그만하자, 가자.
Not until you swear!
맹세하기 전까지는 안돼!
Swear in front of Aries, you'll never leave us!
양자리 앞에서 맹세하세요. 넌 절대 우리를 떠나지 않을 거야!
Now!
지금!
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
I'm sorry, Aries.
미안해, 양자리.
I've said this before, and I'll say it again.
전에도 이런 말을 한 적이 있는데, 다시 말씀드리죠.
I'm not leaving Section E.
난 섹션 E를 떠나지 않을 거야.
Yes!
예!
Won’t karma get you for that?
카르마가 당신을 그렇게 하지 않을까요?
That's your decision.
그건 당신의 결정입니다.
I hope you won't regret it.
후회하지 않기를 바랍니다.
You just lost your chance to be with your father.
넌 방금 기회를 잃었어 아버지와 함께 계십시오.
So stupid!
정말 바보같아!
That's what you used to blackmail Jay-jay?
그게 네가 Jay-Jay를 협박하던 방식이었어?
Are you forgetting who I am?
내가 누군지 잊고 있는 거야?
I always get what I want.
나는 항상 내가 원하는 것을 얻습니다.
Tss.
쯧쯧.
Don't worry, Jay.
걱정하지 마세요, 제이.
I promise I'm gonna connect you to your father.
약속할게, 그럴게 당신을 아버지에게 연결해 주세요.
How did you know I was here?
내가 여기 있다는 걸 어떻게 알았나요?
Uhh, Edrix said you're hanging out here to get some air.
어, Edrix가 너랑 놀고 있다고 했어 여기 바람 좀 쐬러 왔어.
It hasn't even been a week of classes, yet you got into a fight already.
수업이 일주일도 안됐는데, 그런데 당신은 이미 싸웠어요.
My hands hurt.
손이 아파요.
Do it for me.
나를 위해 해주세요.
Ouch!
아야!
Be gentle!
부드럽게 행동하세요!
Who told you to get into a fight then?
그럼 누가 싸우라고 했나요?
Always losing your temper.
항상 화를 냅니다.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Wow! You're getting good at apologizing, huh.
우와! 사과하는 데 능숙해지고 있군요.
"I'm sorry". Say it one more time.
"죄송합니다". 한 번 더 말해보세요.
One more, come on. One more time.
하나 더, 어서. 한 번 더.
Stop making fun of me.
나를 놀리지 마세요.
I only apologize to you.
나는 단지 당신에게 사과할 뿐입니다.
Why just me?
왜 나만?
I'm sure you've got a long list of people you need to apologize to.
나는 당신이 사람들의 긴 목록을 가지고 있다고 확신합니다 당신은 사과해야합니다.
Who's first? Aries, and then—
누가 먼저요? 양자리, 그리고—
I don't care.
나는 상관하지 않는다.
I don't have feelings for any of them.
나는 그들 중 누구에게도 감정이 없습니다.
Only for you.
오직 당신만을 위한 것입니다.
Whatever!
무엇이든!
Please stay.
머물러주세요.
Keifer…
키퍼…
I'm not giving up on you, Jay.
난 당신을 포기하지 않아요, 제이.
I'll fight for you.
나는 당신을 위해 싸울 것입니다.
What kind of dream was that?
그것은 어떤 꿈이었나요?
That didn't happen, but it felt so real.
그런 일은 일어나지 않았어 하지만 정말 현실감이 느껴졌습니다.
Enough, Jay-jay!
그만해, 제이제이!
Good morning, Jay! See you.
좋은 아침이에요, 제이! 또 봐요.
Ci-N?
Ci-N?
I went ahead, Jay!
내가 먼저 갔어요, 제이!
You’re impossible to wake, you just kept on groaning.
당신은 깨어날 수 없습니다. 너 계속 신음소리만 냈잖아.
Shit!
똥!
That brat's really gonna get it from me later.
그 새끼 진짜 당할 거야 나중에 나한테서.
He actually left me?
그 사람이 정말 날 떠났나요?
And even brought my bike with him!
그리고 심지어 그와 함께 내 자전거도 가져왔습니다!
- What? - Looks like you're late too.
- 무엇? - 너도 늦은 것 같구나.
I woke up late, how about you?
늦게 일어났는데, 당신은 어때요?
I woke up late, too.
나도 늦게 일어났어요.
Okay, let's go.
좋아, 가자.
What’s with you?
당신은 무엇입니까?
Don’t look back.
뒤돌아보지 마세요.
- Why? - Someone's following us.
- 왜? - 누군가 우릴 따라오고 있어요.
Wait, don't look.
잠깐, 보지 마세요.
What?
무엇?
Call Keifer.
키퍼에게 전화하세요.
Huh?
뭐?
Quickly.
빠르게.
Wait, wait.
잠깐만요.
There's the girl.
저기 그 소녀가 있어요.
Jay, run!
제이, 도망쳐!
Hey!
여기요!
Jay-jay, I told you to leave, why are you still here?
Jay-jay 내가 떠나라고 했잖아 왜 아직도 여기에 있나요?
Jay, leave!
제이, 떠나요!
The girl!
그 소녀!
I won't leave you alone here!
나는 당신을 여기에 혼자 두지 않을 것입니다!
Go!
가다!
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
I'm good, are you okay?
난 괜찮아, 괜찮아?
What was that?!
그게 뭐였지?!
You thought you won already?
이미 이겼다고 생각했나요?
That's just a hint of what's about to come.
그것은 앞으로 다가올 일에 대한 힌트일 뿐입니다.
What do you need from us?
우리에게 필요한 것은 무엇입니까?
Her.
그녀의.
We know she's Keifer's girlfriend.
우리는 그녀가 Keifer의 여자친구라는 것을 알고 있습니다.
Huh?! He's not my boyfriend!
뭐?! 그 사람은 내 남자친구가 아니야!
He said it so himself that we're not in a relationship!
그 자신도 그렇게 말했다. 우리는 관계에 있지 않습니다!
Do you think we'll believe you?
우리가 당신을 믿을 것 같아요?
Jay, we need to escape them.
제이, 저 사람들로부터 탈출해야 해요.
How?
어떻게?
Just surrender Keifer's girlfriend to us so it's over with.
그냥 Keifer의 여자친구를 항복시키세요 우리에게는 끝났습니다.
This guy's annoying.
이 사람 짜증나.
Insist it all you want, I'm not his girlfriend!
원하는 대로 다 주장하세요. 나는 그의 여자 친구가 아닙니다!
And it'll be a bigger mess if I give her to you.
그리고 그건 더 큰 혼란이 될 거야 내가 그녀를 당신에게 준다면.
Jay!
어치!
We’ll go ahead.
계속하겠습니다.
Where are you?
어디세요?
Why do I feel like something is wrong?
왜 뭔가 잘못되었다는 느낌이 들까요?
Were you able to contact her?
그 사람한테 연락은 됐어요?
You don't have to hide it from me.
나에게 숨길 필요는 없습니다.
I already know.
나는 이미 알고 있다.
I'm saying this so it's clear…
내가 이렇게 말하는 건 분명하니까…
I'm not backing down.
나는 물러서지 않을 것이다.
Even if we're engaged already?
우리가 이미 약혼했는데도요?
I don't care.
나는 상관하지 않는다.
Let Jay-jay decide.
Jay-jay가 결정하게 하세요.
I'll only stop when she tells me to.
나는 그녀가 나에게 말했을 때만 멈출 것입니다.
Why is Jay-jay still not here?
제이제이는 왜 아직도 안오나요?
Do you know where she is?
그녀가 어디에 있는지 아시나요?
No.
아니요.
Keifer!
키퍼!
The tracker shows Jay-jay is in the hospital.
트래커에는 Jay-jay가 표시됩니다. 병원에 있어요.
What?!
무엇?!
Drix, go!
드릭스, 가!
Boys, over here!
얘들아, 여기야!
Where are you Jay?
제이는 어디에 있나요?
I'm going crazy.
나는 미쳐 가고있다.
Miss, is there a Jasper Jean Mariano here?
아가씨, 벽옥 있나요? 여기 장 마리아노?
Wait Sir, I'll check.
잠깐만요 선생님, 확인해 보겠습니다.
Faster, Miss!
빨리요, 아가씨!
I don't have time!
시간이 없어!
Sir, there's no Jasper Jean Mariano admitted here.
선생님, 재스퍼가 없어요 Jean Mariano는 여기에 동의했습니다.
- Huh? - What time was she admitted?
- 뭐? - 몇시에 입원했나요?
A while ago, check it again! Faster!
얼마 전, 다시 확인해 보세요! 더 빠르게!
Sorry Sir, but there's—
죄송합니다만, 거기에는—
Miss, check it again please.
아가씨, 다시 확인해 주세요.
Guys, here!
여러분, 여기요!
Jay!
어치!
Jay, I’m coming.
제이, 나 갈게.
Good thing the wound isn't that deep.
다행히 상처는 그렇게 깊지 않다.
You shouldn't be lifting heavy things for one week.
들어올리면 안 돼 일주일 동안 무거운 일을.
Where's Jay-jay?
제이제이는 어디 있지?
She was right there a while ago.
그녀는 얼마 전 바로 거기에 있었습니다.
She disappeared all of a sudden, she was probably shocked by all the blood.
그녀는 갑자기 사라졌고, 그녀는 아마도 모든 피에 충격을 받았을 것입니다.
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
I don't know, bro.
모르겠어요, 형.
She just started shaking when she saw me bleeding.
그녀는 방금 흔들리기 시작했어요 내가 피 흘리는 걸 봤을 때.
She didn't talk...
그녀는 말을 하지 않았어요...
she just kept on crying.
그녀는 계속 울기만 했어요.
Fuck.
못쓰게 만들다.
Ever since Ram's gang weakened,
Ram의 갱단이 약해진 이후로,
everyone popped out of nowhere.
모두가 갑자기 튀어 나왔다.
And they all want to get Jay-jay
그리고 그들은 모두 Jay-jay를 원해요
because she's Keifer's girlfriend.
왜냐하면 그녀는 Keifer의 여자친구이기 때문이죠.
I don't even know.
나도 모르겠어요.
I'm just grateful that David came to help us.
그것만으로도 감사해요 다윗은 우리를 도우러 왔습니다.
If it wasn't for him, we wouldn't even reach the hospital.
그 사람이 아니었다면, 우리는 병원에도 갈 수 없었어요.
Rory, your coffee.
로리, 커피.
Next time, call me.
다음에는 나한테 전화해.
Don't try to be a fucking hero.
빌어먹을 영웅이 되려고 하지 마세요.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
How is she?
그녀는 어때요?
She looked terrified when I found them.
그녀는 겁에 질려 보였다 내가 그들을 찾았을 때.
With all that blood, I thought it was her who got stabbed.
그 모든 피를 가지고, 나는 칼에 찔린 사람이 그녀라고 생각했습니다.
But she was just hugging Rory.
하지만 그녀는 단지 로리를 껴안고 있을 뿐이었습니다.
Why did this happen?
왜 이런 일이 일어났나요?
What stupid shit did Keifer do this time for Jay-jay to get involved again?
케이퍼가 이번에 무슨 멍청한 짓을 한 거야? Jay-jay가 다시 참여하게 하려면?
They all want to use Jay-jay to beat Keifer.
다들 사용하고 싶어해요 Jay-jay가 Keifer를 이겼습니다.
Huh?
뭐?
Keifer never uses his head!
키퍼는 절대로 머리를 사용하지 않습니다!
So, what's your plan?
그래서, 당신의 계획은 무엇입니까?
None yet.
아직 없습니다.
But when I get back, they better prepare themselves.
하지만 내가 돌아왔을 때, 그들은 스스로 준비하는 것이 더 좋습니다.
Why?
왜?
Why didn't I black out?
나는 왜 정신을 잃지 않았습니까?
Why didn't I attack them like how I did to Cyrus and Ram?
나는 왜 그들을 공격하지 않았는가 내가 사이러스와 램에게 했던 것처럼요?
A lot has happened ever since I wore this uniform.
그 이후로 많은 일이 일어났어요 나는 이 유니폼을 입었다.
Stop it!
그만해요!
But among all of them, this one's the worst.
그러나 그 중에서도, 이게 최악이에요.
Jay!
어치!
Keifer…
키퍼…
No, no.
아니, 아니.
Don't cry.
울지 마세요.
I'm here, don't cry.
나 여기 있어요, 울지 마세요.
Please don't cry, I'm here.
제발 울지 마세요. 제가 여기 있어요.
Don't cry, it's okay.
울지 마세요, 괜찮아요.
I'm here.
나는 여기 있다.
Don't cry.
울지 마세요.
It's okay.
괜찮아요.
Is this your blood?
이게 당신의 피인가요?
Are you hurt?
상처받았나요?
No.
아니요.
I thought the same incident with Ram would happen again.
나도 같은 사건인줄 알았는데 Ram과 함께 다시 일어날 것입니다.
I was scared.
나는 무서웠다.
It's okay, everything's okay.
괜찮아, 다 괜찮아.
Everything’s okay.
모든 것이 괜찮습니다.
Stop crying.
울지 마세요.
It's okay.
괜찮아요.
I saw lots of blood
피를 많이 봤어
but I didn't faint nor harm anyone.
그러나 나는 기절하지도 않았고 누구에게도 해를 끼치지 않았습니다.
And we'll figure out why.
그리고 우리는 그 이유를 알아낼 것입니다.
But for now, let's get you cleaned up.
하지만 지금으로서는 당신을 깨끗하게 해주세요.
I know this is wrong because Yuri's my fiancé already.
난 이게 잘못된 걸 알아요 왜냐면 유리는 이미 내 약혼자야.
But why do I feel this way?
그런데 나는 왜 이런 기분이 들까?
When it comes to Keifer,
Keifer의 경우
my feelings are certain.
내 감정은 확실해요.
Wait, what are you going to do?
잠깐만요, 뭘 할 건가요?
You need rest.
휴식이 필요합니다.
Just shut up and let me.
그냥 닥치고 내버려 두세요.
I'm not giving up on you, Jay.
난 당신을 포기하지 않아요, 제이.
I'll fight for you.
나는 당신을 위해 싸울 것입니다.
Is this still a dream?
아직도 꿈인가요?
Shit, someone wake me up!
젠장, 누가 나 좀 깨워줘!
Game on.
게임이 시작되었습니다.
Don’t just let them take what’s yours.
그들이 당신의 것을 가져가도록 놔두지 마십시오.
Just because they dared to make a bold move.
그들이 감히 그랬기 때문에 과감한 조치를 취하기 위해.
Follow your heart.
당신의 마음을 따르십시오.
Don't listen to distractions and don't give them an inch.
주의를 산만하게 하는 말을 듣지 마세요 그리고 그들에게 1인치도 주지 마세요.
Were you the one who taught them?
그 사람들을 가르친 사람이 당신이었나요?
Out of all the boys in Section E, five of us can do Martial Arts.
섹션 E의 모든 소년들 중에서 우리 중 다섯 명은 무술을 할 수 있어요.
Six if you include Mayo too.
Mayo도 포함하면 6개입니다.
Oh "kapour"!
오 "카푸르"!
- "Kapour!" - Parkour!
- "카푸르!" - 파쿠르!
You said "kapour"!
"카푸르"라고 하셨죠!
Stupid, it's parkour!
바보야, 파쿠르야!
If I'm the stupid one, then what are you?
내가 바보라면, 그럼 넌 뭐야?
Attention-seeker!
관심을 끄는 사람!
Asshole!
항문!
Profanity.
욕설.
I'm jealous.
나는 질투한다.
I can't help it, Jay.
어쩔 수 없지, 제이.
You agreed to be my fiancée.
당신은 내 약혼자가 되기로 동의했습니다.
Fuck, it's because of Jay-jay?!
젠장, 제이제이 때문이라고?!
Wait, no!
잠깐, 안돼!
It isn't what it looks like!
그것은 보이는 것과 다릅니다!
Kit!
전부!
Even blaming Kit!
심지어 키트를 비난하기도 합니다!
Stop talking to Jay-jay like that!
제이제이한테 그런 식으로 얘기하지 마세요!
Go flirt with everybody in Section E!
섹션 E에 있는 모든 사람과 시시덕거려 보세요!
You're no different from Ella, anyway!
당신은 Ella와 다르지 않습니다. 어쨌든!